- 吸血鬼后裔前情提要  - 我用了黑魔法
Previously on Legacies... I did black magic.
这是黑魔法容器
This is a Mora Miserium,
这个工具是用来收压住
the tool used to withhold
这类魔法带来的副作用的
the ill effects of such magic.
只要它不碎
So long as it doesn't shatter.
我们把它丢到一个魔法无法流窜出去的地方
We drop it in a place where magic can't escape.
- 监狱世界  - 绝对不行
The prison world. Absolutely not.
他是绝对不会让我们靠近那个关押着
He's not gonna let us anywhere near that prison world
- 我们疯子舅舅凯的监狱世界的  - 邦妮  邦妮
with our psychotic uncle Kai. Bonnie! Bonnie!
那如果我们把它送到另一个世界呢
Then what if we sent it to a different one?
在新的星盘创建一个新世界
Make a new world with a new ascendant
不受杀人狂魔老舅的干扰
and no homicidal uncles.
之后  当所有人都沉浸在
And then, when everyone else
女巫聚会的祈福环节时
was basking in Coven Day bliss,
我把两个星盘联在一起了
I linked the two ascendants.
你做了什么  阿莉莎
What did you do, Alyssa?
我把他们都送走了  就像你把其他人送走那样
I sent them away. Just like you sent the others.
- 你把塞巴斯蒂安赶走了  对不对  - 他自己选择离开的
You kicked Sebastian out, right? He chose to leave.
老爸  我们在哪
Dad, where are we?
监狱世界  你们小的时候亲手创建的世界
Prison world. It's the one you made when you were kids.
你好啊  伊丽莎白
Hello, Elizabeth.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian.
总共五个人
Five total.
没错  有人吸干了他们的血
Yeah, somebody fed on them.
十年前
把尸体烧了意图毁尸灭迹
Burned the bodies to cover it up.
或许不是我们当中的人
It might not be one of ours.
瑞克  我们该怎么做
Ric, what are we gonna do?
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第13集
你骗我
You lied to me?
如今
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
你跟我说塞巴斯蒂安自己选择离开学校的
You told me that Sebastian chose to leave the school.
我说他做出了自己的选择  他不肯遵守我们的规则
I said he made his choice. He refused to respect our rules.
所以你把他送到这来了么
So you sent him here?
他有帮手  是一个女巫
He had help. There was a witch
施的咒语
who did the spell.
黑头发  温柔的双眸
Dark hair, kind eyes.
口音也很好听
Amazing accent.
艾玛
Emma.
你怎么能这样  爸
How could you, Dad?
翻 译  岛岛
等咱们武装好自己之后你再吼我吧
You can yell at me after we arm ourselves.
爸  为什么我们如此急需武器
Dad, why do we need weapons so bad?
你们只需要知道  我们深陷危险当中
All you need to know is that we're in danger,
而且我们得立马想办法出去
and we need to find a way out now.
翻 译  silver
我们现在身处一个新世界
We're in a new world now.
或许你不再是这儿的老大了
Perhaps you are no longer the one in charge.
翻 译  JoaH
翻 译  晁安
我话先搁这了  我女儿们跟我要离开这里
To be clear, my daughters and I are leaving,
你接着留在这  还有  没错  我还是这的老大
you are staying behind and yes, I am in charge.
我的天啊
: Oh, my God.
特效：小螺号
爸  此事事关凯  对不对
Dad. This is about Uncle Kai, isn't it?
校 对   岛岛
所以你才会这么担心
That's why you're so worried?
我知道这事对你来说不容易
I know this has to be hard for you,
特 效   麦 斯
但是你说他已经成了干尸了
but you said he was desiccated.
你不知道他的能耐
You don't know what he's capable of.
在我确保没有人能够让他重获自由之前
And until I'm positive no one's set him free,
我绝对不会冒任何风险
I'm not taking any chances.
爸  谁会让他重获自由
Dad, who could have set him free?
待会解释
I'll explain all that later.
现在  我得让你去牧场那去
Right now, I need you to go to the meadow
在其他人之前抢先拿到沙漏
and get the Sandclock before anyone else finds it.
之后你们就得回到这里藏身
Then I need you to come back here and hide.
不要暴露行踪
And stay hidden.
爸  这都是我的错
Dad, this is all my fault.
如果我一开始没有用黑魔法
If I hadn't done black magic in the first place,
我们就不会沦落至此
we'd have never been in this mess.
我们都会犯错
We all make mistakes.
我不敢相信居然会发生这种事
I-I can't believe that this is happening.
真的对不起  塞巴斯蒂安
I'm so sorry, Sebastian.
你爸反应过激不是你的错
You are not responsible for your father's overreactions.
你到底做了什么让他如此恼怒
What did you do to upset him so much?
他想让我远离你
He wanted to keep me away from you.
我很高兴你在这
I'm glad you're here.
姑且撇开当前的情况不说
Circumstances aside.
- 但是我们不该留在这里  - 别担心
But we should not stay here. Don't worry.
等我们找到出去的办法  你会跟我们一起出去
When we find a way out of here, you're coming with us.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
你错解我的意思了
You... you misunderstand me.
我指的是这个房子
I meant this house.
这个镇子
This town.
外面的世界非常广阔  伊丽莎白
There's a whole world out there, Elizabeth.
我们坐拥这一整个世界
We have an entire planet to ourselves.
所以跟我走吧  去享受这一切
So come with me and experience it.
就这一天
Just for one day.
我不能  我爸爸说
We can't. My dad said...
他再一次欺骗了你  相信我吧
He lied to you. Again. Trust me...
外面没有任何人
...there is no one else here.
这个人过着奢华的花天酒地的生活
* This one got a princely racket *
这正是我所说的
* That's what I said now *
他的夹克上印着夸张的印章  却脑袋空空
* Got some big seal upon his jacket, ain't in his head now *
你若嫁给他  你的父亲将会默许你
* You marry him, your father will condone you *
现在又如何呢
* How about that now? *
你若嫁给我  你的父亲便要跟你断绝关系
* You marry me, your father will disown you. *
敬启者
我独自一人
* All by myself *
但是我不想如此
* But don't want to be *
我独自一人
* All by myself. *
莉兹
Lizzie?
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian?
你们在哪呢
Where are you guys?
快答问题
Quick question.
你他妈是谁
Who the hell are you?
洁德
Jade?
十年前
别闹了  温蒂
Knock it off, Wendy.
你肯定会把整个地方烧个一干二净的
You're gonna burn the place down.
行吧  监狱长
Okay, Warden.
你只是因为去不了你的麻瓜聚会而感到沮丧罢了
You're just upset you can't go to your Muggle party.
好吧  我都答应伊内兹我会去的了
Yeah, well, I told Inez I was gonna be there,
现在她肯定觉得我在耍她了
and now she's gonna think that I flaked on her.
没错  屏障咒还生效着呢
Yep, the barrier spell is still up.
我最讨厌被关禁闭了
I hate being locked up.
行吧  以防万一你没注意  我的情绪也不太稳定呢
Yeah, well, in case you didn't notice, I got issues, too.
而且跟一个狂躁的狼人困在一起
And being stuck in detention with an edgy werewolf
非常刺激我的情绪波动
is triggering 'em.
要知道  如果你能管得住自己的话
You know, we wouldn't even be here
我们都不会被困在这了
if you could just control yourself.
不是我  要怪就怪变身
It's not me. It's the turn.
每当月圆之夜降临
When the full moon's coming,
总是会发生些什么
something just happens to me.
你是指  你变成一头狼这事么
You mean, like, you become a wolf?
去你的吧
Oh, screw you.
你根本不知道这是什么感受
You got no idea what it feels like,
感受着你身体的每一根骨头断裂
to feel every bone in your body break.
这将是你有生以来所经历的最大的痛苦
It's worse than any pain you've ever felt.
好  你说服我了
Okay, you've convinced me.
生活真是又惨淡又不公平  所以放松点
Life is awful and unfair. So relax.
禁闭的时间可漫长了
Detention's gonna last as long as it lasts.
除非
Unless...
嘿  小乔
Hey, Joze.
你在做什么呢
Hi. What you doing?
你在偷看我吗
You spying on me?
这是迪亚戈和温蒂
This is Diego and Wendy.
她就是能够操纵火元素的那个女巫
She's the witch who does fire.
没错  我们被咒语困在这了
Yeah, we're spelled in here.
现在我们得错过一个非常精彩的派对了
And now we're gonna miss this really awesome party
而且我们超级想去
that we wanted to go to.
你就是传说中特别的虹吸女巫中的一员吧
Aren't you one of those special siphon witches?
我相信你可以毫不费劲地
I bet you could take this barrier spell down
搞定这个屏障咒的
with no problem.
不  不可能
No. No way.
这也太难了  只有年长的女巫才能做到
No, that's too hard. Only advanced witches can do that.
除非  我是说
Unless... I mean,
你觉你能搞定这种只有年长女巫才能施的咒语吗
you think you could handle a big girl spell like that.
我不该这么做的
I'm not supposed to.
不  没关系的
No, it's all right.
我们去了派对就回来
We'll go to the party and then be back
不会有人发现我们不见了的
before anyone even realizes we're gone.
你说呢  小乔  你跟我们站在一边吗
What do you say, Joze? You one of us?
小乔茜·萨尔茨曼长大了
Little Josie Saltzman all grown-up.
震惊啊
I'll be damned.
莉兹也在这吗
Is Lizzie here, too?
不
Uh, no.
洁德  你怎么会在这
Jade, what are you doing here?
如果你不介意的话
If it's okay with you, can we
咱们能不能在我进食之后
have this conversation
再谈这事
after I eat?
因为我可饿坏了
Because I'm starving,
你看着又那么美味
and you look delicious.
想活命的话跟我来
Come with me if you want to live.
欢迎光临  我叫它帕克堡
Welcome. I call it Fort Parker.
虽然有点发霉  但是还得收租
It's a... it's a bit moldy but also rent-controlled,
所以我尽量不抱怨环境问题了
so I try not to complain.
调味伏特加要么  这其实
Flavored vodka? It's, uh...
不是什么纯麦威士忌  再次声明  这玩意本来就不存在
It's no Zima, but then again, nothing is.
你就是凯·帕克
You're Kai Parker.
就是在下
I am.
而你是萨尔兹曼双胞胎之一
And you are one of the Saltzman twins.
我能嗅到你身上的双子味儿
I can smell the Gemini on you.
你是
are you
琳达么  还是乔安妮
Linda or, or Joanie?
我总是分不清你俩
: I can never tell you two apart.
乔茜
I'm Josie.
这是我母亲的名字  就是被你杀害的那位
Named after my mom, who you killed.
好吧  跑得了和尚跑不了庙  严格来说
Okay, here we go. Look, technically,
我当时想杀的是你和你的妹妹
I was trying to kill you and your sister.
但是现在已经翻篇了
Uh, but that's all over now,
所以依我看  咱们都往前看吧
so I say we just move on.
往前看
Move on?
你就是个禽兽
You're a monster.
我要是禽兽就让你死在那了
A monster would have let you die.
那个想把你变成她
That vampire who tried to turn you
专属血饮的吸血鬼
into her own personal Capri Sun?
才是真正的禽兽
She's the real monster.
她和自己那帮同党统治这个世界
She and her cronies run this world.
他们将我从干尸状态下唤醒
They revived me from desiccation
好让自己能有个玩物
just so they could have a little plaything.
他们每天  定时定点地
Every day, like clockwork,
跟玩一些猎杀游戏
they hunt me down and kill me.
但因为我跟这个世界存在某种神奇的纽带
But s... since I'm magically bound to this world...
我死不透
...I can't actually die.
所以我在此出现只是为了被猎杀
So I pop back up only to be hunted
被一遍又一遍的屠杀
and killed all over again
日复一日
every day.
欢迎来到超自然版的饥饿游戏
Welcome to the Supernatural Hunger Games.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
那女孩之前
That girl used to go
在我们学校上学  为什么会来这儿
to my school. Why is she here?
世上没有免费的午餐
No answers for free.
情报换情报
Information for information.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
我用了一个黑魔法容器
I, um... I used a Mora Miserium.
沙漏么
Sandclock?
别告诉我  它裂了  然后
Oh, don't tell me. It degraded, and you
你打算把东西丢我这儿
just decided to drop it over here
都不为我的安全考虑一下
without a thought for my safety.
我试图创造一个新世界  但被一个女巫耍了
I tried to create a new world, but a witch tricked us,
我们就被吸入了这个世界里面
and we got pulled into this one instead.
典型局中局啊
Classic double cross.
还有
And, uh...
我们指谁
who's "we"?
我回答了你的问题
I answered your question.
现在你该为我解惑了
Now you have to answer mine.
洁德为什么在这儿
Why is Jade here?
嗯
Yeah.
这事你不该问我
I'm not the one you should be asking.
今晚谁在呢
Who is out there tonight, huh?
是达蒙还是邦邦  或者是凯瑟琳
Is that Damon? Bon-Bon? Katherine?
不管你是谁  都要去找
Well, whoever you are, that one goes out
阿拉里克·萨尔茨曼
to Alaric Saltzman!
对的  就是因为他
All right, 'cause he's the reason
我才能站在这里说话
I am walking and talking and...
肆意歌唱  我们都很感激他
: and singing, which I know we're all grateful for.
谢了  里克
So thanks, Ric, for...
把一堆你控制不了的学生丢了进来
dumping a bunch of students you couldn't control over here,
因为他们无聊的时候
'cause the second they got bored, they...
唤醒了我
woke me up!
还是说是你干的  里克
Or is that you, Ric?
不不不  这不可能
No, no, no, it can't be.
你不会蠢到
You wouldn't be dumb enough
来这里查看我的情况  对吧
to come here and check up on me, would you?
不过悲伤
Oh, but grief is...
是很复杂的情感对吧
is complicated, right?
鳏夫行事诡异
Widowers do strange things.
萨尔茨曼博士
Dr. Saltzman.
见鬼了真是
I'll be damned.
迪亚戈
Diego.
等等
Wait.
说句话啊
Talk to me.
我更愿意让你见识一下
Yeah, you know, I'd rather show you something.
我现在能控制变身了
I can control it now.
再也不会感到疼痛了  毕竟你把我送到这个世界
Doesn't hurt anymore, 'cause you sent me to a world
每天都在重复
where it's always the same day.
每晚
And every night...
都是满月
a full moon.
如此十年
Ten years.
数千次变身
Thousands of turns.
我不知道会这样
I didn't realize...
我不在乎
I don't care.
就像你一样
Like you never did.
是你
You.
我还能说什么
What can I say?
就喜欢心脏
I'm all heart.
看看咱来俩
Hey, look at us--
都留胡子了啊
we're beard bros.
老爸
Dad!
乔茜
Josie.
天呐
Oh, God.
你跟他搞什么  他没准会杀了你啊
What are you doing with him? He could've killed you.
- 其实他救了我  - 我不在乎
He saved my life, actually. I don't care.
他就是个骗子
He's a liar.
你不能相信他  听到没
You can't trust him. You hear me?
他告诉我你把一群老学生
Was he lying when he told me you sent a bunch
送到这里以示惩戒  也是在说谎吗
of your old students here to punish them?
我说了  人都会犯错
I told you, we all make mistakes.
但同样的错  我不会再犯
I'm not about to make the same one twice.
老爸  这个世界里你杀不死他
Dad, you can't kill him in this world.
那至少我得试一下
Well, I'm sure as hell gonna try.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
很好
Good.
房子归你了
'Cause it's yours.
我早该料到会这样
Oh, I should have seen that coming.
好的
: Okay.
第一次杀我  我不计较  里克
First death's free, Ric,
但我警告你
but I'm warning you,
如果你觉得我
if you think that I'm...
我肯定是料不到还有这出
Well, I definitely didn't see this coming.
我不想让他阻止我
I didn't want him trying to stop me.
阻止你干什么
Stop you from doing what?
把咱俩都弄出去
Getting us all out of here--
即使这意味着要与你合作
even if that means partnering up with you.
我们需要三件东西  把我困在这里的天体气象顶点
- So, we need three things-- the apex of the celestial event
一点班尼特的鲜血
that trapped me here, some Bennett blood,
二重星盘
and the duplicate ascendant,
那些小混球把我唤醒之后
which is the first thing I went looking for
- 我第一个找的就是这个 - 你找到没有
when those burnouts woke me up. Did you find it?
世上没有免费的午餐
No answers for free.
你身上应该有带班尼特的鲜血吧
I assume you come carrying the Bennett blood.
你怎么会
How is it possible
进一个监狱世界
that you came to a prison world
却不带一件逃离这里所需的物件呢
without the one thing you need to escape it?
这次旅行计划本不是这样
Well, it's not exactly like this trip was planned.
好的  那咱俩的合作你能带来
Okay, so then what exactly are you bringing
什么助力
to this partnership?
毕竟从我的角度出发  你我之间
Because from where I stand, I'm the only one of us
也就我还有用处
who is not useless.
世上没有免费的午餐
No answers for free.
天体事件是什么
What's the celestial event?
实际上我不清楚  但是
That I actually don't know, but, uh...
还剩这么多时间呢
there's only so many minutes in a day,
- 我早晚能整明白  - 这就是你的计划吗
so I'll figure it out. That's your plan?
排除法么
Mm-hmm. Process of elimination?
我喜欢挑战
I like a challenge.
说实话
And to be honest,
我别的没有  时间有的是
I've got nothing but time.
沙漏能否强大到在没有天体事件的情况下
Could the Sandclock be strong enough to power the ascendant
给星盘供给能量
without a celestial event?
或许吧
Maybe.
何出此言  沙漏在哪
Why? Where is it?
显然在这里的某处啊
Somewhere in this clearing.
那我怎么没看见
Then why don't I see it?
因为我施了咒
Because I put a spell on it.
就算摆在你眼前  也看不到
You wouldn't even know that you were looking at it.
还别说  之前也有人用这一套在泰迪熊玩偶上下咒
You know, that-that actually happened to me
用来对付我
with a teddy bear once.
你
You, uh...
实际上并不信我  是吧
you really don't trust me, do you?
就当我是以示诚意吧
Consider it a show of good faith.
你骗我
You were lying.
学得真快
You're definitely learning.
谢谢
Thank you.
这已经是我这一生  印象最深刻的一次约会了
This has already been the most amazing date of my life.
我不想结束
: I don't want it to end.
或许也没必要结束
Perhaps it doesn't have to.
到时候还是得回去
We have to go back at some point.
我家人会找我的
My family will be looking for me.
我们可以说服我爸  让他知道自己错看了你
We can convince my dad that he was wrong about you.
他只是
He just...
需要时间
needs time.
恐怕这行不通
That's not going to work, I'm afraid.
因为我没打算回去
Because I'm not going back.
我希望留在这个世界
I wish to remain in this world...
希望你留下来陪我
and I want you to stay with me.
你确定这样有用吗
Are you sure this is gonna work?
我们为什么会来这
Why are we here?
情报换情报哦
Oh. Information for information.
再跟我多讲一些马里之洼的事
Tell me more about this Malivore pit
还有你们之前解决的那些怪物
and those monsters you've been dealing with.
声明一下  我从未怀疑过圣诞老人的真实性
And for the record, I never lost faith in Santa being real.
马里之洼基本上也就是一个口袋维度  像这个一样
Basically, Malivore is a pocket dimension, like this one.
里面有一个通往我们世界的入口
There is a portal into our world.
我们关上了  但怪物还是不断涌来
We closed it, but the monsters keep coming.
厉害了
Fascinating.
回答一下你的问题
Now, to answer your question,
我们来这是因为在被那些人
we're here because I spent years
当成猎杀运动用的玩物时
studying genealogical records
我花了很多年研究系谱记录
while being hunted and killed for sport.
我最近发现有人
I recently found someone
以史密斯菲尔德的名义捐了血
who donated blood under the name Smithfield,
这是她的夫姓
which was her married name.
娘家名是班尼特
Bennett.
班尼特的血
Bennett blood.
谢天谢地你在这
Thank God you're here.
我还是很饿
I'm still hungry.
- 我还以为你杀了她  - 我肯定是杀了
I thought you killed her. Yeah, I totally did.
不过他们像我一样被放逐到这个世界
But they're banished to this world, like me,
所以他们也会不算死而复生
so they just keep... coming back.
我们该走了
We should go.
乔茜
Josie?
那是我的心脏吗
Is that mine?
好奇怪啊
Weird.
好了
Now...
我们到哪一步了
where were we?
等等
Wait.
- 先别杀他  小迪  - 让我猜猜看
Don't kill him yet, D. Let me guess.
- 你想烧死他  - 可以
You want to burn him. Sure.
但首先我得跟他聊聊
But first I want to have a chat.
还记得他是如何让我们接受审判
Remember how he put us on trial
然后又把我们抛弃在这个可憎的地方吗
and then abandoned us to this god-awful place?
我觉得是时候
I think it's time
审判你了
for your trial...
阿拉里克·萨尔茨曼
Alaric Saltzman.
我们得在狼人醒来之前找到我爸
We need to find my dad before that werewolf wakes up.
那就去啊
Well, then go.
去救爸爸
Save Daddy.
我支持你哦
I'm rooting for you.
因为你和你爸不属于这个地方
Although you and your dad aren't bound to this place,
所以到了某个时刻  今天 明天  或者后天
- so at some point-- be it today, tomorrow or the next--
他们会把你俩都杀了的
they'll kill you both.
抱歉了孩子  班尼特之血不见了
Sorry, kiddo, the Bennett blood's gone.
我们被困在这里了  什么都不重要了
We're trapped here. Nothing matters.
如果还有一个方法可以拿到班尼特之血呢
What if there was another way to get Bennett blood?
那你会帮我吗
Would you help me then?
嗯  又想操控我
Yeah, nice try at manipulation,
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
但我不会再相信你说的任何
but I'm not gonna believe anything y...
这是我们把沙漏送过来的时候  我从邦妮那里拿的
It's Bonnie's from when we sent the Sandclock here.
我就知道你对我有所保留
I knew you were holding out on me.
因为我不知道自己能否相信你
I didn't know if I could trust you.
好吧
Okay.
天啊
Oh, goodness.
时间刚刚好  宝贝
Oh, perfect timing, baby.
一动不动
Immobilus.
谢谢你帮忙啊
Hey, thanks for your help.
你的直觉是对的
Your instincts were right.
你是不能相信我的
There is no trusting me.
所以你还在这玩跳棋呢
So, while you've been playing checkers...
我已经在下国际象棋了
I've been playing chess.
将军咯
Checkmate.
关于整个饥饿游戏啥的呢  有一点我忘说了
Yeah, I guess I forgot to mention one thing about
我还挺享受的
- the whole Hunger Games-- I'm kinda into it.
没那么单调了
Keeps the monotony interesting.
等他们让我苏醒  他们就会很快意识到
Once they woke me up, they quickly realized my
我卓越的领导才能
superior leadership qualities.
他们就像我的追随者一样
They're kind of like my followers,
可以这么说吧
I guess you could say.
你这破沙漏自己留着吧
You can keep your lousy Sandclock.
破掉之前我就已经离开了
I'll be gone before it breaks.
笑一个
Oh, chin up.
你刚刚开始学习骗人  会慢慢掌握精髓的
You're new at conning people. You'll get better at it.
带她去找里克
Take her to Ric.
先别杀了她
Don't kill her yet.
让他们俩吃足苦头
Make them both suffer.
没有你帮忙我做不到的  孩子
I couldn't have done it without you, kid.
这下好玩了
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
好安静啊
It's so quiet. Mm-hmm.
我那个时代  每天都是这样的
This is what it was like every day in my time.
一切都不紧不慢  安静祥和  我好怀念啊
Things were peaceful, unhurried. I miss it.
如果你有了我这么敏锐的听力
But when you have my hearing,
你就会发现现代世界简直吵死人了
the modern world is terribly noisy.
而且  唯一让我喜欢的  只有你
In fact, the only thing I like about it is you.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian,
我不能留下来
I can't stay.
好吧  你想想
Okay. Think,
想一下  维也纳
- think about this-- Vienna,
北京  佛罗伦萨
Beijing, Florence.
你可以带着皇冠
You can wear the crown jewels
住在凡尔赛宫啊
and live in Versailles.
这个世界只属于我们俩
This world belongs only to us.
不是这么简单的
It's not that simple.
我还有我爱的家人
I have a family that I love,
而你可以长生不老
and you won't age.
我不是被放逐到这个世界的  所以我会老的
I wasn't banished to this world, so I will.
我有办法
I have a solution for that.
让我把你变成吸血鬼吧
Allow me to turn you into a vampire.
如果你是想折磨我
If you're planning on torturing me,
那你会失望了  我受得住的
you're gonna be disappointed. I can handle the torture.
那如果是
How about
看你女儿受折磨呢
seeing your daughter be tortured?
乔茜
Josie.
乔茜  你没事吧
Josie, are you okay?
暂时没事  但之后发生什么
For now, but what happens next
取决于你
is up to you.
开口吧
So talk.
因为我已经等了十年了
'Cause I've waited ten years
等你解释一下为什么这么对我们
for an explanation for what you did to us.
是你们让我别无选择
What other choice did you leave me?
告诉我  怎么会这样的
Tell me, how did this happen?
不知道
No idea.
你们三个说服乔茜把你们从留堂教室放出来了
The three of you convinced Josie to let you out of detention.
温蒂和迪亚哥都不肯交代
Wendy and Diego aren't talking.
洁德  你跟他们不一样
Jade, you're not like them.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
你是好孩子  你乐于助人
You're a good student. You care about people.
你申请医学院  因为你想救死扶伤
You're applying to med school because you want to save lives.
告诉我  发生了什么
Talk to me. Tell me what happened.
帮我理解一下  因为这一切
Help me understand because this,
可不是你能干出来的
this... isn't you.
那或许你不了解真正的我
Yeah, well, maybe you don't know the real me.
其中一个受害者  她叫伊内兹
One of the victims, her name's Inez.
你的展板上还挂着你们俩的照片
There's a picture of you two on your bulletin board.
你为什么要撕裂她的喉咙
Why did you rip her throat out?
我没在场
I wasn't there.
她手里拿着这个
She was holding this.
是你的
It's yours.
你就惩罚我们就行了
So just go ahead and punish us.
你都已经决定好了
You've already made up your mind.
是啊
Right.
我知道我该干什么
I knew what I had to do.
五个人  被残忍谋杀了
Five people were dead, brutally murdered.
被蚕食
Fed on,
撕扯  分尸
ripped apart, dismembered,
又毁尸灭迹了
burned to cover it up.
而你们没有任何一个人
And not one of you showed any remorse
有一点悔过之心  也不承认自己的罪行
or even admitted what you had done.
我不能让你们继续待在学校
I couldn't let you stay at the school.
也不能把你们放出学校
I wasn't gonna unleash you into the world.
所以你就永远的
So you sent us here
把我们关在这里了
forever?
你就这么帮助你误入歧途的学生们吗
Is that how you help your students?
不
No.
我错了
I made a mistake.
我应该杀了你们的
I should have killed you.
在面临死亡之前还这么能说啊
Ooh, doubling down in the face of imminent death.
真是有种
Ballsy.
我知道你们都是凶手
I knew you were killers,
死性不改
that you wouldn't change.
是卡洛琳让我对你们仁慈一点
It was Caroline that talked me into showing you mercy.
够了  杀了他吧
Enough talk. Let's kill him.
不  我要让他先吃点苦头
No. I want him to suffer first.
你们去看下凯  他有了能让我们出去的所有物件
You two go check on Kai. He has all the pieces to get us out now.
确保他不会扔下我们
Make sure he doesn't leave us behind.
你那么坚信你是对的
You're so sure you're right.
不如我来告诉你那晚到底发生了什么吧
How about I tell you what actually happened that night?
伊内兹邀请我去森林里聚会
Inez invited me to a party in the woods.
我们已经打情骂俏
We'd been flirting
好几个月了
for a few months.
我觉得我终于有机会可以看看
I thought it was my chance to finally see
她到底喜不喜欢女生了
if she was really into girls or not.
温蒂也很想来
Wendy really wanted to come,
而且也想引起迪亚戈的注意
and she was trying to get Diego to notice her,
所以就说服我把他也带上了
so she talked me into bringing him, too.
嘿
Hey.
我很开心你来了
I'm glad you came.
厉害  伊内兹竟然
Wow. Inez actually got
带了三个寄宿学校的白痴来了
three of the boarding school losers to show up.
他在说什么
Wh-What's he talking about?
那是个怪咖聚会
It was a freak party.
他们在比谁能带来最怪的怪咖
Seeing who could get the biggest weirdo to show up.
他们看我们一眼
Yeah, they took one look at us,
就知道
and they just...
我们和他们不同
they knew we were different.
走吧
Let's go.
看着啊
Check this out.
迪亚戈  不要
Diego, don't.
那时候就应该结束了的
It should have ended there.
我本可以阻止他的  但我僵住了
I could have stopped it, but I froze.
或许我不想证明他们是对的
Maybe I didn't want to prove them right
好像我们真的是异类
about us being different.
又或许我内心一部分
Or maybe part of me
是想让他们死的
wanted it to happen.
之后的事情都太模糊了
Everything after that's a blur.
报警啊
Somebody call the cops!
不要  不行
No! Don't!
但我那晚确实发现了一件事
I did find out something that night.
我是个杀人狂
I'm a ripper.
不
No! No.
洁德   不要
Jade, please.
不要啊
No, Jade.
对不起了
I'm so sorry.
不
No!
那是我这辈子最不堪的时刻
That was the worst moment of my life.
你以为我毫无悔意
You think I didn't feel any remorse for what happened.
但我有
But I did.
羞愧
Shame.
内疚
Guilt.
惶恐
Panic.
我再也忍受不了这种感受了
I couldn't bear feeling all of it anymore.
所以
So...
我决定不去想了
I decided not to.
我那天晚上就把我的人性关了
I shut off my humanity that night.
我也曾尖叫着求助过
I was screaming for help.
你就是听不到
You just couldn't hear it.
但是在这里
But being here...
你把我们送进来的地方
...where you sent us,
我杀了凯  迪亚戈和温蒂几千次
I've killed Kai, Diego, and Wendy thousands of times.
也许你说得对
So maybe you're right after all.
我终于变成了你认为的那个杀手
Because I've finally become the killer that you thought I was.
抱歉我没发现你关闭人性的那些征兆
I'm sorry I didn't recognize the signs.
你忙着保护你女儿呢
You were too busy protecting your daughters.
你一向很擅长这个
You're good at that.
那就让我们一起看看你保护的怎么样吧
Let's just see how good.
跟我来
Come with me.
我想玩个游戏
There's a game I want to play.
你没什么要说的吗
Have you nothing to say?
还是说你的沉默意味着你已经做出决定了
Or does your silence mean that you've already made a decision?
嗯
Yes.
我决定了
I've decided.
我无法下决心
I can't make this decision yet.
我有想过变成吸血鬼
I've thought about becoming a vampire.
我当然会想过这个问题
Of course I've thought about it.
如果我成了吸血鬼  我和乔茜就不用合并了
If I did, there wouldn't be a Merge.
我也会青春永驻
And my skin would stay flawless forever.
但那样我就
But I also...
再也无法生孩子了
wouldn't be able to have kids.
我也不能跟一个人携手到老
I couldn't grow old with someone.
我甚至不知道这些东西是不是我想要的
And I don't even know if those are things that I want.
但关键是
But that's the point.
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
在我想清楚之前我不能草率做出决定
I can't make this decision until I'm sure.
我就怕
I was afraid
你会这么说
that you would say that.
所以是时候你该知道
So it's time that you knew
这不是一个任你安排的选择
that what I'm offering isn't a choice.
这是我自己的选择
: Yes, it is.
我不会喝吸血鬼的血的
I'm not gonna drink vampire blood.
你已经喝了
You already have.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian...
你做了什么
what have you done?
我只是想护你周全
What I had to to keep you safe.
这才是有趣的部分
And this is the fun part.
同样的游戏我们也跟凯玩了
It's what we do with Kai.
简单点说就是捉迷藏
Basically, it's hide-and-seek.
你跑开藏起来
You run and hide...
而我负责找你
and I seek.
我拒绝
No.
拒绝无效
Uh, yes.
要不我就去找乔茜玩
Or else I will hurt Josie.
我对她可不会手下留情的
I will hurt her so bad
她会跪在我脚下祈求我杀了她的
that she will be begging for me to kill her.
来吧  这很好玩的  你知道吗
Come on. It's supposed to be fun. You know what?
我给你五分钟时间藏起来
I'll even give you a five-minute head start.
如果你能活过24小时且不被我捉到的话
And if you can survive being hunted for 24 hours,
我会放你女儿一条生路的
I will let your daughter live.
我是说  这才是你真正关心的事情对吧
I mean, that's all you really care about, right?
好吧
Fine.
玩吧
Let's play.
伊丽莎白  你听我解释
Elizabeth, you must listen to reason.
我绝对不会做任何伤害你的事情的
I would never do anything to hurt you.
- 你要相信我  - 放开我
- You must believe me. - Let me go.
听我说
Please listen to me!
拜托
Please.
我曾经喜欢过的一个女巫死在了我面前
I once cared for a witch who died in front of me.
她那时没有机会获得永生  但是你有
She didn't have a chance to become immortal, but you do.
我在尽力保你  但如果你还不明白
I am trying to help you, but if you cannot see that,
那么只能我为你做这个决定了
then I must make the choice for you,
因为我真的太
because I love you
爱你了
too much.
你听到了吗
Can you hear that?
我爱你  我不能再失去你了  卡桑德拉
I love you, and I will not lose you again, Cassandra.
伊丽莎白  我说的是伊丽莎白
Elizabeth. I meant Elizabeth.
我想我们应该跟其他人见个面了
I think we should see other people.
洁德
他去哪了
Where the hell is he?
凯·帕克耍了我们
Kai Parker screwed us.
该死的
I'll be damned.
乔茜·萨尔茨曼耍了我
Josie Saltzman screwed me.
神秘瀑布镇
谁
Who is this?
谢天谢地
Thank God
你还活着啊  担心死我了
you're still alive. I was worried sick.
嘿  不得不说
Hey, I got to say,
关于那个储血瓶的事  我真的一点都不
I'm not even mad about the whole
生气
blood con.
甚至还蛮为你自豪的
Borderline proud, even.
好吧  我这人一直以来都疯疯癫癫的
Okay, I'm-I'm always mad.
但却是那种有趣的  令人捉摸不透的疯癫
But in a fun, completely unpredictable sort of way.
这样倒是可以让人时时刻刻保持警觉
It keeps you on your toes.
- 我恨你  - 嗯
- I hate you. - Yeah.
这么说也太伤人了吧
That's such a Ric thing to say.
嘿  你爸爸现在怎么样了
Hey, how is the old man nowadays?
我恨你对我的家人所做的一切
I hate you for everything that you've done to my family,
我永远不会帮你离开这里的
and I am never helping you get out of here.
你就是个骗子  你说的这些我都无所谓
You're a liar, and nothing you ever say will matter to me.
事实上我给你打电话是想帮你出去的
Actually, I called to help you get out.
还有另外一种法子
There is another way.
那我现在说的话你还有所谓吗
Does what I say matter now?
- 我不相信你  - 行  好吧  完全可以理解
- I don't believe you. - Yeah, okay, that's totally understandable.
但你还拿着沙漏  对吧
But you still got Darth Vader's alarm clock, right?
也许吧
Maybe.
好
Good.
你需要借助它的力量
'Cause you're gonna need every last bit
来完成这件事
of its power to pull this off.
别再相信他了
So much for trusting him.
做爱体验感不错哟 谢了 —凯
- 你男朋友把我们留在这儿了  - 好吧
- Your boyfriend left us here. - Yeah, well,
不管怎么说我对女孩子更感兴趣
it's a good thing I prefer girls anyway.
再说  我一点也不在乎那家伙
Besides, I don't care about that guy.
我现在只想找到萨尔茨曼
All I care about right now is finding Saltzman.
用定位咒可不像你的风格
A locator spell isn't very sporting of you.
谁让他罪有应得
Yeah, well, let the punishment fit the crime.
我记得  我记得  我记得
* I remember when, I remember, I remember when... *
那个地方总有让人欣喜的东西
* There was something so pleasant about that place *
当你出门在外  不够谨慎
* And when you're out there, without care *
我无法联系到你
* Yeah, I was out of touch *
萨尔瓦托寄宿学校
- 不会吧  - 他在这儿
- No way. - He's here.
但这并不是因为
* But it wasn't because *
我知道的还不够
* I didn't know enough... *
不  他在我们脚下
No. He's beneath us.
他在隧道里
He's in the tunnels.
你一生中最重要的时刻
* The time of your life... *
他在军械库  那里有什么
He's at the armory. What is that?
管他呢  我们去抓他
Who cares? We'll find him.
他也没法反抗
And he won't put up much of a fight.
来吧  你是谁
* Come on now, who do you... *
我该走了
I should probably get going.
你肯定不敢相信的
You're not gonna believe this,
但我找到了出去的办法
but I found my own way out of here.
什么  什么办法
What? How?
秘密哟  小乔茜
Oh, no answers for "fwee," little Josette.
佑护汝之魂
* Ha, bless your soul... *
你让我想起了她
You know, you remind me of her.
你的亲生母亲也觉得她比我聪明
Your bio-mom thought she was smarter than me, too.
但我惩罚了她
But I punished her just like I'm about
就像惩罚你那样
to punish you.
因为  你准备好了吗
Because... You ready for it?
要想使用沙漏  你就必须先得打破它
In order to use that Sandclock, you have to break it.
当你被黑魔法击中的时候
And when you get hit with all that black magic,
如若它杀不了你  它会把你
if it doesn't kill you, it's gonna turn you
拖进黑暗变成恶魔的
into something dark and evil.
但你同样
But you'll also be
也会拥有无比强大的力量足以让你离开这里
powerful enough to make your own door out of here, so,
多么尴尬的处境  对吧
what a predicament, right?
为了救爸爸
To save Daddy,
为了回家
to get yourself home,
你就必须得变成一个恶魔
you have to become a monster.
就像我一样
: Like... me.
况且你也不会记得我跟你说的这些的
The only catch is, you won't remember I told you any of this,
因为你根本不会记得我
because you won't remember me at all.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
你知道你在哪了
I know where you are.
嘿  谢谢你给我讲的马里之洼的故事
Hey, thanks for all the stories about Malivore.
一个通往另一个维度的入口
A portal to another dimension
对于现在这个处境来说倒也不失是一种好办法
sounds pretty good to me right about now.
不不不  马里之洼
No, no, no. Malivore
是一种通往地狱的维度  那里面是极致的黑暗
is a hell dimension. It's eternal darkness.
你会被困住  饱受孤独的
You'll be trapped and alone.
嗯  我的一生都在经历这些
Yeah, I've been trapped and alone for most of my life.
我需要换个环境了
I could use the change of scenery.
所以如果我是你的话
So, I'd smash that Sandclock
我会在接下来的几秒内打破沙盘
in the next few seconds if I were you,
因为我马上就要跳下去了
'cause I'm about to take a swan dive
我不希望你忘记了
into oblivion, and I'd hate for you
唯一能救你的东西
to forget the only thing that can save you.
是它让我疯狂吗
* Does that make me crazy? *
祝你好运  孩子
: Good luck, kiddo.
是它让我疯狂吗
* Does that make me crazy? *
是它让我
* Does that make me *
疯狂吗
* Crazy? *
也许
* Probably. *
哈喽
Hello.
他妈的  我做到了
Oh, son of a bitch. I made it.
你是什么生物
And who might you be?
你和我之前遇到过的任何怪物都不一样
You're quite unlike any monster I've ever encountered.
伙计
Buddy.
你不知道的可多了去了
You don't know the half of it.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）